<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="help_title">Info</string>
    <string name="help_subtitle">Fast answers to the usual questions.</string>
    <string name="help_search_placeholder">Search the info</string>
    <string name="help_no_results">Nothing matched. Try another word.</string>

    <string name="help_section_getting_started">First steps</string>
    <string name="help_section_installing">Setting up</string>
    <string name="help_section_in_game">Inside the game</string>
    <string name="help_section_content_updates">Content &amp; updates</string>
    <string name="help_section_about_app">About the app</string>
    <string name="help_section_saves_cleanup">Worlds &amp; cleanup</string>
    <string name="help_section_reach_out">Get in touch</string>

    <string name="faq_account_q">Do I need to register?</string>
    <string name="faq_account_a">Not at all. No login, no email, no password to keep track of. Just open the app and dive in.</string>

    <string name="faq_need_internet_q">Do I need to stay online the whole time?</string>
    <string name="faq_need_internet_a">Only for browsing the catalog and downloading. As soon as a mod sits on your phone, you can play without a connection (as long as Minecraft itself runs offline).</string>

    <string name="faq_supported_versions_q">Which Minecraft versions are supported?</string>
    <string name="faq_supported_versions_a">Android Minecraft Bedrock — the newest release plus a handful before it. Each mod spells out the exact versions it fits, look right by the file.</string>

    <string name="faq_how_install_q">How do I set up a mod?</string>
    <string name="faq_how_install_a">Open the mod, choose a file from the list, tap download, then install. Minecraft will launch and pull it in by itself. Final step — flip the pack on in the world you want to play.</string>

    <string name="faq_install_pack_q">And texture packs and skins?</string>
    <string name="faq_install_pack_a">Exactly like mods. Once installed, enable them in Minecraft — textures sit under Global Resources, skins under your Profile.</string>

    <string name="faq_install_fail_q">Why won\'t the mod install?</string>
    <string name="faq_install_fail_a">A few things to check first:\n• The mod has to match your Minecraft version — see the version line on the mod page.\n• Your phone needs free storage.\n• Quit Minecraft and open it again (this fixes it more often than you\'d think).\nStill stuck? Re-download the file and try once more.</string>

    <string name="faq_download_stuck_q">The download is frozen at 0% and won\'t move</string>
    <string name="faq_download_stuck_a">If the progress bar refuses to move, your internet provider is most likely blocking the server the mods sit on — sometimes entire regions or carriers get cut off and there\'s nothing we can do from our end. Switch on a VPN, kick off the download again, and it should race through. Once the file is on your phone you can turn the VPN off — the mod itself doesn\'t need it.</string>

    <string name="faq_corrupted_file_q">I hit a \"file corrupted\" error</string>
    <string name="faq_corrupted_file_a">That means the download stopped partway. Delete what you\'ve got, fetch it again on a steady connection (Wi-Fi if possible) and you should be set.</string>

    <string name="faq_mod_not_visible_q">I installed the mod but nothing shows up in the game</string>
    <string name="faq_mod_not_visible_a">The mod is already in Minecraft, you just need to switch it on. Open your world\'s settings and enable the pack. A few mods also need Experimental Features enabled — same settings menu.</string>

    <string name="faq_experimental_q">How do I enable Experimental Features?</string>
    <string name="faq_experimental_a">While creating or editing a world, scroll to Experiments and flip on the toggle your mod asks for (the mod usually names it — often \"Holiday Creator Features\" or \"Beta APIs\"). Reload the world afterwards.</string>

    <string name="faq_lag_q">The game stutters after installing a mod</string>
    <string name="faq_lag_a">Some mods are simply demanding. Worth trying, in order:\n• Close other apps sitting in the background.\n• Lower the render distance in Minecraft (this helps the most).\n• Nudge graphics quality down a step.\nIf it\'s still choppy, the mod may be too heavy for the device — go for a lighter one.</string>

    <string name="faq_multiplayer_q">Can I run mods on a server with friends?</string>
    <string name="faq_multiplayer_a">It depends on the server. Normally every player needs the same packs installed — if the server you\'re joining allows the mod, you\'re good. If it doesn\'t, the mod simply won\'t do anything there.</string>

    <string name="faq_new_mods_q">Do you keep adding new mods?</string>
    <string name="faq_new_mods_a">Constantly. Pull to refresh the catalog and you\'ll spot whatever landed since your last visit.</string>

    <string name="faq_updates_q">How do I tell if a mod was updated?</string>
    <string name="faq_updates_a">Whenever the mod author releases a new version, we bring it into the catalog. The version sits right beside the file on the mod page.</string>

    <string name="faq_safety_q">Are the mods safe?</string>
    <string name="faq_safety_a">They are. Every mod is checked before it lands in the catalog — no viruses, nothing shady tucked inside the file.</string>

    <string name="faq_ads_q">Why are there ads?</string>
    <string name="faq_ads_a">Servers and updates cost money, and ads are how we cover them — that\'s what keeps the app free for you. We do our best to keep them out of the way while you\'re actually using it.</string>

    <string name="faq_no_internet_q">It says \"no internet\" but mine is working</string>
    <string name="faq_no_internet_a">If your connection is fine and the app still complains, our servers are probably taking a short nap. Wait a few minutes and try again.</string>

    <string name="faq_uninstall_q">If I remove this app, do I lose my mods?</string>
    <string name="faq_uninstall_a">You don\'t. The mods now live inside Minecraft — they stick around even if our app is gone.</string>

    <string name="faq_safe_for_saves_q">Will mods ruin my worlds?</string>
    <string name="faq_safe_for_saves_a">Not by themselves. Mods are added as packs in Minecraft and you decide which world they go into. If you\'re testing a new mod and don\'t want to risk a world you care about — spin up a fresh world for it.</string>

    <string name="faq_remove_mod_q">How do I remove a mod I\'m done with?</string>
    <string name="faq_remove_mod_a">Inside Minecraft, open Packs (Behavior, Resource, or Skin depending on the type), long-press the one you want gone, and choose Delete. Your worlds stay untouched — only the mod goes.</string>

    <string name="faq_report_issue_q">Where do I let you know something\'s broken?</string>
    <string name="faq_report_issue_a">Use the Feedback section on the Suggest screen. Describe what happened — the more detail you share, the quicker we can crack it.</string>

    <string name="faq_submit_mod_q">I built my own mod — can I send it over?</string>
    <string name="faq_submit_mod_a">Absolutely. Open the Suggest screen and drop a link or attach the file there. We go through submissions and add the ones that fit.</string>

</resources>
