<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- Installation -->
    <string name="faq_how_install_q">How do I install a mod?</string>
    <string name="faq_how_install_a">1. Open the mod card.\n2. Tap a file from the list.\n3. Press Download and wait.\n4. Tap Install — Minecraft will open and import the pack.\n5. Switch the pack on inside the world you want to play.</string>

    <string name="faq_install_pack_q">How do I install a texture pack or a skin?</string>
    <string name="faq_install_pack_a">The flow is the same as for a mod. After import, enable it in Minecraft under Global Resources, Behavior Packs, or in the Profile menu for skins.</string>

    <string name="faq_install_fail_q">The mod won\'t install. What should I check?</string>
    <string name="faq_install_fail_a">• Check that the mod supports your Minecraft version — the compatible range is shown at the bottom of every mod card.\n• Free up some space on your device.\n• Close Minecraft and this app, then try again.</string>

    <string name="faq_corrupted_file_q">I get a \"file corrupted\" error</string>
    <string name="faq_corrupted_file_a">Most often the download was interrupted.\n• Delete the mod and try again.\n• Make sure your connection is stable during the download.\n• If it still fails, switch from mobile data to Wi-Fi (or the other way around).</string>

    <!-- Using mods in the game -->
    <string name="faq_mod_not_visible_q">I installed a mod but I don\'t see it in Minecraft</string>
    <string name="faq_mod_not_visible_a">• Open World Settings and turn the pack on manually.\n• Enable Experimental Features for that world.\n• Try a fresh world with the pack already attached.</string>

    <string name="faq_experimental_q">How do I enable Experimental Features in Minecraft?</string>
    <string name="faq_experimental_a">In Minecraft go to Create New / Edit World → Experiments and turn on the toggles your mod needs (commonly Holiday Creator Features, Custom Biomes, Beta APIs). Restart the world after enabling.</string>

    <string name="faq_multiplayer_q">Can I use mods in multiplayer?</string>
    <string name="faq_multiplayer_a">It depends on the server. Most servers require every player to have the same packs installed — if the host allows the mod, you\'re good.</string>

    <string name="faq_lag_q">The game lags after installing a mod</string>
    <string name="faq_lag_a">Some mods are heavy on weaker devices.\n• Close other apps running in the background.\n• Lower render distance and graphics quality in Minecraft.\n• Try a lighter mod from the same category.</string>

    <!-- App & content -->
    <string name="faq_supported_versions_q">Which Minecraft versions are supported?</string>
    <string name="faq_supported_versions_a">We target the latest Bedrock release and a few previous versions. Each mod card lists the exact compatible range.</string>

    <string name="faq_new_mods_q">Will you add new mods?</string>
    <string name="faq_new_mods_a">Yes — fresh mods and updates land on the catalog regularly. Pull down on the catalog to refresh and see the latest additions.</string>

    <string name="faq_updates_q">How do I know when a mod is updated?</string>
    <string name="faq_updates_a">Each file in the mod card shows its version. Update notifications are on our roadmap — for now, refresh the catalog from time to time.</string>

    <string name="faq_safety_q">Are these mods safe?</string>
    <string name="faq_safety_a">Every mod we publish is reviewed by hand. No viruses, no hidden trackers, no shady payloads inside the .mcpack files.</string>

    <!-- Account, data, connectivity -->
    <string name="faq_account_q">Do I need an account to use the app?</string>
    <string name="faq_account_a">No. Everything works without registration — favorites and downloads stay on your device.</string>

    <string name="faq_need_internet_q">Do I need internet?</string>
    <string name="faq_need_internet_a">Only to browse and download. Anything already imported into Minecraft works fully offline.</string>

    <string name="faq_no_internet_q">The app says \"No internet\" but my connection works</string>
    <string name="faq_no_internet_a">Usually that means our servers are temporarily under maintenance — we already know about it. Try again in a few minutes.</string>

    <string name="faq_uninstall_q">What happens to my mods if I uninstall this app?</string>
    <string name="faq_uninstall_a">Nothing. Once a mod is imported into Minecraft it lives there — uninstalling our app doesn\'t remove anything from the game.</string>

    <!-- Feedback & contribution -->
    <string name="faq_report_issue_q">Something is broken. Where do I report it?</string>
    <string name="faq_report_issue_a">Open the mod card and tap \"Not working\". Or use the Feedback tab on the Propose screen — describe the problem and we\'ll look into it.</string>

    <string name="faq_submit_mod_q">I made a mod — how can I share it?</string>
    <string name="faq_submit_mod_a">Tap the button below to jump to the submission screen. Drop a link or attach the file and we\'ll review it.</string>

    <string name="faq_submit_mod_btn">Submit a mod</string>

    <string name="faq_ads_q">Why does the app show ads?</string>
    <string name="faq_ads_a">Ads keep the app free and let us update mods without a paywall. We try to keep them out of your way — no popups while you\'re playing.</string>

</resources>
