<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- Getting started -->
    <string name="faq_account_q">Do I have to sign up?</string>
    <string name="faq_account_a">Nope. No login, no email, no password to remember. Just open the app and go.</string>

    <string name="faq_need_internet_q">Do I always need internet?</string>
    <string name="faq_need_internet_a">Only to browse the catalog and download stuff. Once a mod is on your phone, you can play offline (as long as Minecraft itself works offline).</string>

    <string name="faq_supported_versions_q">Which Minecraft versions work?</string>
    <string name="faq_supported_versions_a">Android Minecraft Bedrock — the latest version and the few before it. Every mod tells you which exact versions it\'s for, look near the file.</string>

    <!-- Installing -->
    <string name="faq_how_install_q">How do I install a mod?</string>
    <string name="faq_how_install_a">Open the mod, pick a file from the list, hit download, then install. Minecraft will pop up and grab it on its own. Last step — turn the pack on inside the world you want to play.</string>

    <string name="faq_install_pack_q">What about texture packs and skins?</string>
    <string name="faq_install_pack_a">Same flow as mods. After installing, switch them on inside Minecraft — textures live under Global Resources, skins under your Profile.</string>

    <string name="faq_install_fail_q">Why doesn\'t the mod install?</string>
    <string name="faq_install_fail_a">Quick checks first:\n• The mod must match your Minecraft version — see the version line on the mod page.\n• Your phone needs free space.\n• Close Minecraft and reopen it (this one fixes it surprisingly often).\nStill nothing? Download the file again and retry.</string>

    <string name="faq_corrupted_file_q">I got a \"file corrupted\" error</string>
    <string name="faq_corrupted_file_a">Means the download cut off halfway. Delete what you have, grab it again on a stable connection (Wi-Fi if you can) and you should be good.</string>

    <!-- In the game -->
    <string name="faq_mod_not_visible_q">I installed the mod but I don\'t see anything in the game</string>
    <string name="faq_mod_not_visible_a">The mod is in Minecraft, you just have to switch it on. Open your world\'s settings and enable the pack. Some mods also need Experimental Features turned on — same settings menu.</string>

    <string name="faq_experimental_q">How do I turn on Experimental Features?</string>
    <string name="faq_experimental_a">When you create or edit a world, scroll down to Experiments and flip on the toggle your mod needs (the mod usually tells you which one — often \"Holiday Creator Features\" or \"Beta APIs\"). Reload the world after.</string>

    <string name="faq_lag_q">The game lags after I installed a mod</string>
    <string name="faq_lag_a">Some mods are just heavy. Things to try, in order:\n• Close other apps running in the background.\n• Lower the render distance in Minecraft (this one helps the most).\n• Drop graphics quality a notch.\nIf it\'s still rough, the mod might be too big for the device — try a lighter one.</string>

    <string name="faq_multiplayer_q">Can I use mods on a server with friends?</string>
    <string name="faq_multiplayer_a">Depends on the server. Usually every player needs the same packs installed — if the server you\'re joining allows the mod, you\'re fine. If it doesn\'t, the mod just won\'t do anything there.</string>

    <!-- Content & updates -->
    <string name="faq_new_mods_q">Are you adding new mods?</string>
    <string name="faq_new_mods_a">All the time. Refresh the catalog and you\'ll see what showed up since last time.</string>

    <string name="faq_updates_q">How do I know if a mod got updated?</string>
    <string name="faq_updates_a">When the mod author ships a new version, we add it to the catalog. The version sits right next to the file on the mod page.</string>

    <string name="faq_safety_q">Are the mods safe?</string>
    <string name="faq_safety_a">Yeah. Every mod gets checked before it goes into the catalog — no viruses, no weird stuff hiding in the file.</string>

    <!-- About the app -->
    <string name="faq_ads_q">Why are there ads?</string>
    <string name="faq_ads_a">Servers and updates aren\'t free, and ads are how we pay for them — that\'s how the app itself stays free for you. We try to keep them out of your way while you\'re actually using the app.</string>

    <string name="faq_no_internet_q">It says \"no internet\" but my internet works</string>
    <string name="faq_no_internet_a">If your connection is fine and the app still shouts about it, our servers are probably napping for a bit. Give it a few minutes and try again.</string>

    <string name="faq_uninstall_q">If I delete this app, do I lose my mods?</string>
    <string name="faq_uninstall_a">No. The mods live inside Minecraft now — they stay there even if our app goes.</string>

    <!-- Saves and cleanup -->
    <string name="faq_safe_for_saves_q">Will mods mess up my worlds?</string>
    <string name="faq_safe_for_saves_a">Not on their own. Mods are added as packs in Minecraft and you choose which world they go into. If you\'re trying a new mod and don\'t want to risk a world you care about — start a new world for it.</string>

    <string name="faq_remove_mod_q">How do I delete a mod I don\'t want anymore?</string>
    <string name="faq_remove_mod_a">Inside Minecraft, open Packs (Behavior, Resource, or Skin depending on the type), long-press the one you want gone, and pick Delete. Your worlds stay safe — only the mod is removed.</string>

    <!-- Reach out -->
    <string name="faq_report_issue_q">Where do I tell you something is broken?</string>
    <string name="faq_report_issue_a">Use the Feedback section on the Propose screen. Write what happened — the more detail you give us, the faster we can figure it out.</string>

    <string name="faq_submit_mod_q">I made my own mod — can I send it to you?</string>
    <string name="faq_submit_mod_a">Sure thing. Open the Propose screen and drop a link or attach the file there. We look through submissions and add the ones that fit.</string>

</resources>
